LOGAN COLLINS

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

+1-516-654-4426

@ hermes8527@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Brewlabs

= 04/2023 - 03/2024

https://brewlabs.info/

- Created the company landing page using React from the Figma design, featuring simple yet elegant components and smooth animations
- Created UI kit and unit test script to expedite front-end development for landing pages and on-chain services such as staking
- Developed Smart Contract, wrote unit tests and integrated Web3 in Staking and Zap-In functions

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

SparkWorld*

= 04/2022 - 03/2023

- Collaborated with the CTO to clarify main features of NFT Marketplace and Aggregator
- Developed Smart Contract of NFT Marketplace and wrote unit test scripts in Hardhat framework and fixed several security and performance issues and passed Smart Contract audit
- Deployed Subgraph for NFT Marketplace Smart Contract to track all events and user activities
- Developed a bot in Golang to get NFT sale data and metadata from other NFT Marketplaces on Avalanche and store them in MongoDB as a subproject of NFT Aggregator

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Satang Technologies

iii 04/2020 - 03/2022

- Collaborated with a designer to create a modern, yet simple user interface for company's landing page
- Designed and developed Firo Bridge in Golang to synchronize data between the Firo chain and FiroVM chain and store transaction data in PostgreSQL database to enable Smart Contracts on Firo like Ethereum
- Designed the workflow and developed Smart Contract in Solidity, front-end in Lit, back-end in Golang and integrated Web3 in Asset Tokenizer project to utilize real-estate transactions on the blockchain

Senior Full Stack Developer

Polisport

= 04/2019 - 03/2020

Phttps://polisport.com/, https://polisportvirtualtour.com/

- Joined the company as a Full Stack Web Developer
- Developed RESTful APIs in Node.js to retrieve products and services data and implemented pixel-perfect frontend in React from Figma Design
- · Wrote unit test scripts for the front-end using Mocha and Jest libraries
- Led Polisport Virtual Tour Project and implemented main UI in React and virtual tour in 3d environment using Three.js library

Full Stack Developer

Canary Technologies

= 04/2016 - 03/2019

https://glassbororentals.com/, https://ventano.de/

- During my six-month internship as a developer, I gained valuable insights into the company culture and development methodologies
- In the Glassboro Rentals project, I created smooth and visually appealing user interfaces as a front-end developer
- Designed MySQL database and contributed to three pages using Laravel framework as a Full Stack Developer in the Ventano project

SUMMARY

A seasoned Full Stack Blockchain Developer with 8+ years of experience in the web development industry.

Stepped into the blockchain industry as a Smart Contract and Web3 developer in 2018.

What sets me apart is the ability to learn new technologies, passion for the product and keen eye for detail.

I always create detailed workflows, progress stepby-step, and conduct thorough testing to ensure accuracy and timely development.

I enjoy proposing new ideas, wearing different hats, and collaborating with others to achieve success.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

GPA

DePaul Unversity

 3.9 / 4.0

SKILLS

Git

AWS

GitHub

GCP

Cloud Services

Blockchain				
Solidity	Ethereum	Smart	Smart Contract	
Hardhat	Foundry	Web3	Ethers.js	
Front-end				
React	Vue Typ	eScript	Lit	
Back-end				
Node.js	Golang	Laravel		
Database				
MongoDB	MySQL	Postgr	eSQL	
Development & Operations				
Scrum Agile				
Version Control Systems				

GitLab

Microsoft Azure

Bitbucket